pebblego.com 2019-03-27

# 

  1. **NOTICE/AWARENESS** This policy statement sets forth information practices concerning the type of data that is collected at PebbleGo.com site (the "Web site"). This policy is accessible via a link at the bottom of each page. This policy applies to our online practices only.
  2. **CHOICE/CONSENT** The following paragraphs describe the type of information PebbleGo collects and the reasons why PebbleGo collects the information. By providing the information requested by PebbleGo online forms and by continuing to use the Web site after having an opportunity to review the PebbleGo privacy policy, you have consented to the PebbleGo use of the information it collects as described at the point of collection or in this policy. 

**User Supplied Information** The only information PebbleGo collects is building address, district name, and administrative contact email address(es) and phone number(s). We do not collect or store any student information from the district or building.   
PebbleGo may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) PebbleGo rights or property or other users of the Web site, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. PebbleGo may use or disclose user information to address violations or possible violations of the 

_[Terms of Use](https://pebblego.com/info/termsofuse.html)_ of the Web site. PebbleGo may disclose user information when we believe in good faith that the law requires the disclosure.   
PebbleGo may share aggregate information about our system usage with business partners and other third parties. For example, we may disclose that the Web site audience comes x percent from east of the Mississippi River and y percent from west of the Mississippi River. 

**Children's Information**   
We do not collect ANY personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, or of any age. We do not retain, store and therefore do not need to dispose of any personally identifiable information about children. 

**Your IP Address**  
PebbleGo collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to generate aggregate information, and to audit the use of the Web site. When you request pages from the Web site, our servers log your IP address. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that your session will be logged, but you remain anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our terms of use of the Web site or to protect our service, site, customers or others. 

**Use of Cookies**   
PebbleGo sometimes uses cookies for authentication purposes. There is no personally identifiable information stored within these cookies. We, nor any third party, are able to ascertain any personally identifiable information via these cookies.

  3. **ACCESS/PARTICIPATION**  
You may access the aggregate data collected on the building level usage by PebbleGo about your building level account (no personally identifiable data is collected) through the PebbleGo administration tools, or by sending a request to the address listed below. If you wish to access, remove or correct any building level information you have supplied to PebbleGo you may do so by sending an e-mail request to [support@capstonepub.com](mailto:support@capstonepub.com), or sending a letter via the U.S. Mails to the address below. NO personally identifiable information is collected on students.

    Manager of Web Site Development  
    Pebble Go  
    1710 Roe Crest Drive  
    North Mankato, MN 56003

Please understand that in order to protect your privacy and security, we may also need to take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

  4. **INTEGRITY/SECURITY OF THE DATA COLLECTED**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, PebbleGo has put in place commercially reasonable and appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
 **ENFORCEMENT/REDRESS**  
If for some reason you believe that PebbleGo has not adhered to its privacy policy, please notify us by either of the methods set forth above. PebbleGo will do its best to respond to your concerns and, when appropriate, take steps to correct a problem.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms** By using this Web site, you signify your assent to this policy statement regarding online privacy. PebbleGo may change the terms of its privacy policy with or without notice to you. It is your responsibility to review the terms of this privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy statement, then you may not use the Web site. Your continued use of the Web site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. If you have any questions about this policy statement, the practices of this Web site, or your dealings with PebbleGo, you may contact us at addressed given above. 

**Last Revised: May 25, 2017**  
© 2017 Capstone Publishers
